<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stemapalooza on Learn Robotics Academy</title>
    <link>learnrobotics1.github.io/categories/stemapalooza/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stemapalooza on Learn Robotics Academy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 14:55:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="learnrobotics1.github.io/categories/stemapalooza/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthy Plant Data Lab</title>
      <link>learnrobotics1.github.io/article/healthy-plant-data-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 14:55:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>learnrobotics1.github.io/article/healthy-plant-data-lab/</guid>
      <description>Healthy Plant Data Lab using Arduino Course details Learn how to program the Arduino microcontroller to create an applied electronic device. Hosted by Learn Robotics Instructor: Liz Miller All content can be used for educational purposes. Not for resale or commercial distribution without the prior authorization of Learn Robotics.
Overview Electronics are part of our everyday life, but how do they work? Majority of the devices that we rely on for communication, entertainment, &amp;amp; in business are built on programs, circuits, &amp;amp; sensors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robotics for Elementary Education</title>
      <link>learnrobotics1.github.io/article/robotics-for-elementary-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 14:55:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>learnrobotics1.github.io/article/robotics-for-elementary-education/</guid>
      <description>Elementary Activities with Edison Course details Learn how to program the Meet Edison robot for K-5 elementary education. Hosted by Learn Robotics Instructor: Liz Miller All content can be used for educational purposes. Not for resale or commercial distribution without the prior authorization of Learn Robotics.
Overview Robotics combines programming, electronics, and mechanics into a device that helps us perform tasks in the real-world. We will use the affordable Meet Edison Robot to complete interactive robotics labs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake Simulation using Cubit STEAM kits</title>
      <link>learnrobotics1.github.io/article/earthquake-simulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 10:55:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>learnrobotics1.github.io/article/earthquake-simulation/</guid>
      <description>Earthquake Simulation using Cubit Course details Learn how to integrate electronics in your classroom using a traditional Earthquake STEM lesson. Hosted by Learn Robotics Instructor: Liz Miller All content can be used for educational purposes. Not for resale or commercial distribution without the prior authorization of Learn Robotics.
Overview Robotics combines programming, electronics, and mechanics into a device that helps us perform tasks in the real-world. We will use the affordable Cubit STEAM Kit to complete interactive robotics labs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>